我们学会一件事  起司
Well, if we learned one thing today, C.H.E.E.S.E.
啦啦队长跟强力火药  不能混在一起
is that cheerleaders and high explosives don't mix.
你说的没错  麦克
You can say that again, Mac.
光靠我一个人是不行的   你是个天才
Well, I couldn't have done it without you buddy. You're a genius.
是吗  那为什么我还不会调整录影机的定时功能
Oh, yeah? Well, how come I can't get my VCR to stop blinking 12:00?
你们觉得如何
What did you guys think?
有电话  我来接  我来接
Hey, the phone. I got it. I got it.
喂
Hello.
等一下  乔伊  是你妈打的
Hold on. Joey, it's your mom. It's Mommy.
真的是太棒了
Aw... That's nice.
妈  你觉得如何
Ma, so what did you think?
喔
Well...
那还算好啦
...that was, um, okay.
但说不上是最好
It wasn't the best.
那是我看过最烂的戏了
That was one of the worst things ever...
我说的不只是电视上的表演
...and not just on TV.
我们该对他说什么呢   灯光还不错
What should we say? The lighting was okay.
不行  上次你已经说过灯光不错了  这次轮到我了
Ohh no you don't! You got lighting last time. Lighting is mine.
服装是我的
I have costumes.
太棒了  那我只能说
Oh great! That means I'm stuck with:
"我们看到你在电视上出现  结果你却坐在这里  哇"
"So we were watching you in there, and you were sitting right here. Whoa."
你要说什么呢  菲比  我不知道
What are you gonna do Pheebs? I don't know. I don't know.
我没办法再骗他了  不  我不
I can't lie to him again. Oh, no, I-No.
我要用我的胸部紧紧压着他
I'm just gonna press my breasts up against him.
什么都不说  没错
And say nothing? Uh-huh, yeah, that's right.
哇  我爸妈很喜欢我的表演
Wow, my folks really liked it.
你们有什么看法
What did you guys think?
没那么好吧
It wasn't that good.
老友记   第七季  第04集  瑞秋请助理
Friends  S07E04  The One With Rachel's Assistant
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
菲比  你认为你最喜欢的动物  能代表你吗
Phoebe, do you think that your favorite animal says much about you?
你是指他们背着我说我的坏话
You mean behind my back?
你们一定不会相信  今天我发生了什么事
Oh, Hi you guys, oh my God! you'll never believe what happened to me today.
我坐在办公室里  大家听我说  听我说
I am sitting in my office. You guys! You guys!
你们猜我的经纪人说什么
You're not gonna believe what my agent just told me!
乔伊   我正说到一半呢
Joey! Kinda in the middle of a story here!
抱歉  你继续
Ooh, sorry. Sorry. You finish, go.
我坐在办公室里  你们猜谁走了进来
Okay, so anyway I'm sitting in my office, and guess who walks in.
我要参加两部电视剧的演出
I'm gonna be on two TV shows.
真的是太棒了
That's great.
乔伊  你还没有说完吗
Joey. You weren't finished?
对啊  我的重点只是  "你们猜谁走进我的办公室"
Yeah, "Guess who walks into my office" is my story.
是劳夫罗兰   劳夫罗兰走进我的办公室
It was Ralph Lauren! Ralph Lauren walked into my office.
瑞秋  如果你想说别的事  至少让我把我的事说完
Uh Rach, if you're starting another story, at least let me finish mine.
我说的是同一件事
It's the same story.
哇  这事还真长
Uh, wow, it's really long.
劳夫走进来告诉我   他非常满意我的工作表现
Ralph just came in to tell me that he's so happy with my work...
他要我担任   休闲衫零售部的新销售经理
...that he wants me to be the new merchandising manager for Polo retail.
哇啊
Aw...
你买婚纱还有折扣吗   有啊
Still get a discount on wedding gowns? Yeah.
我真为你感到高兴
I'm so happy for you!
这真的是《我们的日子》
These really are the days of our lives.
什么  喔   既然你们问起
What? Well, since you ask, ha, ha...
他们要我回去演《我们的日子》
They want me back on Days of our Lives.
他们给我涨了很多薪水   嘿
I got—I get a big Pay raise! Oh, hey!
我要饰演德瑞克医生的  双胞胎弟弟史崔克
I'll be playing Drake Ramoray's twin brother, Stryker.
我可以雇用专属助理
I get to hire my own assistant.
我起来太快   现在头很晕
Well-I got a head rush from standing up too fast.
这份工作你做了四年
And you were at this job for four years?
没错  好  你的资历非常棒  西尔达
That's right. well this is all very impressive, Hilda.
我还要问你最后一个问题
Um, I just have one last question for you, uh...
我表现得如何  还可以吧
How did I do? Was this okay?
什么  我从来没有面试过任何人
What? I've never interviewed anyone before.
从来没有人为我工作过
I've actually never had anyone work for me before.
我小时候家里请过佣人   但这完全不一样
Although when I was a kid we had a maid, but this isn't the same.
没错  亲爱的  的确不一样
No, dear, it's not.
我知道
And I know that.
好  谢谢你来面试
All right, well, thank you so much for coming in.
很高兴能认识你   我也是
it was nice to meet you. Thank you! Good meeting you.
好吧
All right.
我还真专业啊
I'm a total pro.
嗨   嗯
Hello. Wow. Huh, um...
嗨  对不起  模特儿面试在走廊尽头的办公室
Hi, yes, I'm sorry. The models are down the hall.
事实上  我是来面试助理的工作
Actually, I'm here about the assistant job.
真的吗
Really?
好吧   我知道了  请坐
Okay, well, then, all right. Well, just have a seat there.
你叫什么名字
Um, so what's--? What your name?
秦格琼斯
Tag Jones.
继续
Uh-huh, go on.
就这样  那是我的全名
That's it. That's my whole name.
那是你的全名  当然
That's your whole name. Of course.
好了  我们来看一下
Okay, let's just have a look-see here.
我从来没有做过办公室工作   工作经验不是很多
I know I haven't worked in an office before. and I really don't have a lot of experience--
你在胡说什么  你当过三年油漆工
Oh come on, What are you talking about? You got three years painting houses...
有两个暑假在星期五餐厅打工
...two whole summers at T.G.l. Friday's.
那些经验很烂  我知道
It's lame, I know.
但我是目标导向的那种人   渴望学习
But I'm a goal-oriented person, very eager to learn--
请等一下
Okay, hold on just a second. please.
抱歉  这是人事部的要求  大家都得这么做  能麻烦你站起来吗
I'm sorry, It's for Human Resources. Everybody has to. Would you stand up?
不  不  不
Ha, ha, no, no, no.
嘿
Hey. Shh, shh, shh.
总之我该走了  好吧  再见
Anyway, I should go. Okay. Bye.
嘿  亲爱的  嗨   甜心
Hey, sweetie. Hi, sweetie.
你们嘀嘀咕咕在说什么
So, what was with all the whispering?
不能告诉你   那是秘密
I can't tell you. It's a secret.
秘密   夫妻不该有秘密的
Secret? Married people aren't supposed to have secrets between one another.
我们深爱并且尊重彼此
We have too much love and respect for one another.
但我还是不能说
But still, no, ha, ha.
我们应该对彼此坦诚一切  我就不会对你隐藏任何秘密
No I'm serious, We should tell each other everything. I don't have secrets from you.
真的吗  告诉我罗斯在大三时  在迪士尼乐园发生了什么事
Really? Okay, So tell me what happened to Ross, junior year at Disneyland.
不   我不能那么做
Oh no-no, I can't do that.
你跟我说  我就告诉你菲比说了什么
If you tell me, I'll tell you what Phoebe said.
好吧  太棒了
okay. okay
罗斯跟我一起去迪士尼乐园玩
So, ahem, Ross and I are going to Disneyland.
我们在一家餐厅吃墨西哥卷饼
and we stop at this restaurant for tacos.
实际上那只是一个家伙  改装了他的车子开的路边摊
When I say restaurant, I mean a guy, a hibachi, and the trunk of his car.
罗斯吃了十个墨西哥卷饼
So Ross has about ten tacos.
总之我们在玩太空车   罗斯开始觉得不舒服
And anyway, we're on Space Mountain and Ross starts to feel a little iffy.
天啊  他吐了吗
Oh, my God. He threw up?
不  他从另一边  把东西全拉了出来
No, he visited a little town south of throw up.
那菲比有什么秘密
So what was Phoebe's secret?
菲比以前的按摩师同事   南西汤普森被开除了
Um, Nancy Thompson, from Phoebe's old massage place, is getting fired.
就那样  我为了那件事  说出迪士尼的秘密
That's it? I gave up my Disneyland story for that?
没错   你输了  笨蛋
Hm, that's right. You lose, sucker!
请你还是要娶我
Please still marry me.
钱德   你有助理吧
Chandler, you have an assistant, right?
她打电话来了吗
Did she call?
你告诉她我病了吧   每次都要说我生病了
You told her I was sick, right? Always tell her I am sick.
不   我只是不知道   你怎么决定要雇用谁
No, I-I just don't know. How do you decide who to hire?
我把选择范围缩小到两个人
I mean I've got it narrowed down to two people.
一个的推荐信很棒   经验非常丰富
One of them has great references and a lot of experience.
还有另外一个家伙   他怎么了
And then, there's this guy. What about him?
我爱他
I love him.
他帅呆了  我真的好想哭
He's so pretty, I want to cry.
我不知道该怎么办了  告诉我
I don't know what to do. Tell me what to do.
少来了  你知道自己该怎么办   你得雇用第一个人
Come on, you know what to do. You hire the first one.
别因为他长得帅就雇他当助理   你得考虑到他们的工作能力
You don't hire an assistants because they're cute. you hire them because they're qualified.
我知道了  你说的有道理  我可以再说一件事吗
No, I hear what you're saying and-and-and that makes a lot of sense but can I just say one more thing?
看他有多帅
Look how pretty.
让我看看
Let me see.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
喔   但还是不行
Oh. But, no.
不  你不能雇用他  因为那么做太不专业了
No. You can't-You can't hire him because it's not professional.
这是给我的   对吧
Um, this is for me, yes?
好吧   你说的对   明天我会雇用西尔达
Okay, you're right. I'll hire Hilda tomorrow.
那个又蠢又老   适合这份工作的西尔达
Dumb, old, perfect-for-the-job Hilda.
让我瞧瞧
Let me see this guy.
哇
Wo-ha-ow!
别让摩妮卡看到照片
Don't show this to Monica.
别告诉她我说  "哇"
And don't tell her about the "Wo-ha-ow!"
《我们的日子》
嗨  乔伊  嗨  泰瑞
Ha, ha, hey, Joey. Hey, Terry.
很高兴能再跟你见面   好久不见
Nice to see you again. Been a while.
真有趣   这里的走廊看起来比以前小
Wow, it's funny these halls look smaller than they used to.
我们搬家了
It's a different building.
那么
So...
史崔克  是吧
...Stryker Ramoray, huh?
我什么时候开始   何不现在就开始呢
When do you want me to start? Why don't we start right now!
这是试镜的剧本
Here are the audition scenes.
试镜  我还以为  你们决定让我饰演那个角色
Audition?  I thought you were offering me the part.
为什么你会那么想呢
Why would you think that?
我演过德瑞克医生  他是史崔克的双胞胎哥哥
I was Doctor Drake Ramoray, Stryker's twin brother.
谁会比我长得更像我呢
I mean, who looks more like me than me, right?
每个人都得参加试镜
Everybody has to audition. Ha, ha.
你知道的  秦瑞  我真的不需要这么做
You know, Terry, I don't really need to do this.
我有自己的第四台电视剧
I got my own cable TV series...
跟机器人搭档演出
...with a robot.
对不起  乔伊  这是规定
I'm sorry, Joey. that's...That's the way it is.
那么
Well...
我猜你以为你很特别
...I guess you think you're pretty special, huh?
你坐在漂亮的小办公室里
Sitting up here in your fancy, small-hailed building...
要大明星在你面前试镜
...making stars jump through hoops for you, huh?
你知道吗
Well, you know what?
我就是那个大明星
This is one star whose hoop--
我就是试演的大明星   试演
This is the star the hoop-This hoop--
我是德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
I was Doctor Drake Ramoray!
嗨   泰格   你来这里做什么
Hi, Tag. What are you doing here?
我特地过来谢谢你  昨天没当着我的面笑我
I just wanted to come by and thank you for not laughing in my face yesterday.
我注意到你办公室里没有植物   所以就帮你带盆植物过来
And I noticed there were no plants  in your office so I brought you your first.
你办公室里有植物
There is a plant in your office.
可以那么说
Kind of.
对
Right.
我猜我不应该在履历表上写着  "注意力敏锐"
So I guess I shouldn't put "good at noticing stuff" on my resume.
谢谢  总之
Thank you. Anyway...
我猜你录取了别人
Anyway...I'm guessing you hired somebody.
那个嘛
Well...
我猜中了
Gotcha.
谢谢你愿意面试我
Thanks again for meeting with me.
但我录取了你
But I hired you.
什么   对   你得到了这份工作
What? Yeah, you got the job.
你是我的新助理   真的吗
You're my new assistant. I am?
对啊
Yeah.
我不敢相信   我也是
I can't believe it. Ha, ha, me either.
那么  首先我要你到楼下
Umm, all right, first thing I need you to do is go downstairs...
找一个叫西尔达的女人   要她回家去
...and find a woman named Hilda, and tell her to go home.
嗨  太好了  你回来了
Hey. Hey, good, you're home.
我想这要比听到  "该死  又是你" 还好
Oh it's always nicer to hear than, "Oh, crap, you again."
甜心  我帮你准备了一个大惊喜
Hey, sweetie, I made you a surprise.
是吗   对   墨西哥卷饼
Oh, yeah? Yeah, tacos.
听完那个故事后   我就一直都想吃墨西哥卷饼
Ever since you told me that story, I've had such a craving for them.
你听不懂那个故事吗
Did you not understand the story?
嗨   嗨   有什么事吗
Hey. Hey, what's up?
没事   我只是想知道晚餐要吃什么
Ah, nothing. Just trying to figure out what I'm gonna do for dinner.
嘿   那是什么   晚餐吗
Hey, ooh, what's that? Dinner stuff?
你在做晚餐   没有
You making dinner? No.
那是什么   墨西哥卷饼吗
What you got over there? Tacos?
不  不是
No. No.
它们只是  只是些
They're umm... They're just, uh-They're--
牛肉包大饼
They're ground beef smileys.
那是墨西哥卷饼
Uh, those are tacos.
对不起   墨西哥先生
Excuse me, Mr. Mexico.
没关系   我不吃了   我还是不敢吃那玩意
Either way, I'll pass. I still can't eat those.
什么事那么好笑
What's so funny?
我没有笑
I'm not laughing.
你跟她说了
You told her!
南西汤普森被开除了
Nancy Thompson's getting fired.
好吧   那时我食物中毒   我不是故意要那么做
Look, Okay, okay. I had food poisoning. It's not like I chose to do it!
我又没有说  "该怎么做才会更好玩呢"
It's not like—It's not like I said, "What would make this ride more fun?"
对  你说的对  抱歉  我不该笑的
Right. You're right, I'm sorry. I shouldn't be laughing.
我应该帮你先铺好报纸
I should be laying down papers for you.
你怎么可以告诉她   我非说不可  我们要结婚了
How could you tell her?! I had to okay?! We're getting married.
夫妻之间不该藏有秘密
Married couples can't keep secrets from one another!
我猜摩妮卡应该知道  在大西洋城发生的事
Oh really? L-I guess Monica should know about Atlantic City.
兄弟
Du--ude!
大西洋城发生了什么事   钱德跟我在酒吧里
What happened in Atlantic City?! Well, Chandler and I are in a bar--
你没有听到我说 "兄弟"吗
Did you not hear me say, "Du--ude"?
有个女孩跟钱德抛媚眼
And this girl is making eyes at Chandler. okay?
一会儿之后  他走过去   一两分钟后我看到他们在接吻
So after awhile he goes over to her and, uh, after a minute or two, I see them kissing.
你不会觉得他是那种会在酒吧里  泡女人的男人
You're thinking, Chandler's  not the type to go to bars and make out with girls.
你是对的   他的确不是那种
And you're right. Chandler's not the type of guy ...
在酒吧里泡女人的男人
...who just goes to bars and make out with "girls."
你跟男人接吻
You kissed a guy?
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
我得为自己辩解下   那时很暗   而且他长得很漂亮
In my defense, it was dark and he was a very pretty guy.
老妹  我笑得很大声
Oh, Mon, I laughed so hard--
你笑到又拉了一裤子了
Ho-ho, so hard we had to throw out your underwear again?
随便你  兄弟  你吻了男人
Whatever, dude. You kissed a guy.
嗨  嗨
Hi. Hey.
西尔达怎么样  适应的还好吧
Ooh, how's Hilda? Is she working out?
喔  我的新助理适应的很好  没错
Oh, my new assistant is working out. Yes.
她很高兴能够得到这份工作吗
Was she happy you gave her the job?
我的新助理非常高兴   我雇用了我的新助理
My new assistant is very happy that I hired my new assistant.
喂
Hello.
嘿   你能等一下吗
Oh, hey! Can you hang on a second?
是《麦克与起司》的制片打来的
It's the producers over at Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E...
先失陪一下
...if you'll excuse me for a minute.
嘿   我没想到你会打来   我正在看下星期的剧本
Hey, funny you should call. I was just looking over next week's script.
取消了
Canceled?
他们不播了
Like, they're taking it off the air? Oh.
好吧   星期一见
All right, I'll see you Monday.
不再拍了
We're not even shooting them anymore!
好吧   再见
All right. Bye.
他们取消了《麦克与起司》
They canceled Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
我很遗憾   我真的很遗憾   乔伊
Oh, sorry. Oh, I'm sorry Joey.
他们为什么要那么做   那出戏很棒  对吧
Why would they do that? It was a good show, right?
你想说秘密吗   好吧   念大学时
You want to tell secrets? Okay, Okay! in college...
罗斯都会穿卫生裤了
...Ross used to wear leg warmers.
好吧   钱德参加模仿香草冰大赛   还拿到了冠军
All right, All right! Chandler entered a Vanilla Ice look-alike contest and won.
罗斯得了第四名   抱头痛哭
Ross came in fourth and cried!
我的天啊
Oh, my God!
那很好笑吗   你觉得那很好笑吗
Oh, is that funny? Oh, You find that funny?
或许钱德也应该   知道你的一些秘密
Well maybe Chandler should know your secrets too.
我什么都告诉他了
Ha, ha. Oh, I-I already told him everything.
你给我闭嘴
You shush!
有一次她被罚不准吃晚餐
Once Monica was sent to her room without dinner...
结果她吃掉了  她用意大利面做的珠宝盒
...so she ate the macaroni off a jewelry box she'd made.
罗斯每个星期六晚上   都待在家里看《黄金女郎》
Ross stayed home every Saturday night to watch Golden Girls.
摩妮卡到13岁才会看时间
Monica couldn't tell time until she was 13.
对有些人就是很难
It's hard for some people!
那当然
Of course it is.
哇
Wow.
钱德曾穿我的内裤去上班   嘿
Chandler one time wore my underwear to work! Hey!
对不起   我想不出来罗斯还有什么糗事
Oh, I'm sorry, I couldn't think of any more for Ross.
在大学时   有一次钱德喝醉了
Ohh! Ohh! In college, Chandler got drunk...
他跟打扫房间的清洁妇上床
...and slept with the lady who cleaned our dorm.
那是你
That was you.
随便   兄弟   你亲了男人
Whatever, dude. You kissed a guy.
这种事怎么会发生在我身上
How could this happen to me?
昨天  我演出两出电视剧  今天  我什么都没有
Yesterday, I had two TV shows. Today, I got nothing.
等一下  《我们的日子》呢
Wait a minute, what happened to Days of our Lives?
他们有点生我的气
Uh, well, they might be a little mad at me over there.
怎么了
What happened?
或许我有点太嚣张了   我告诉他们该怎么做
Well, maybe I got a little upset, and maybe I told them where they could go.
乔伊   你为什么要那么做呢
Joey, why would you do that?
因为  他们要我试镜
Because! They wanted me to audition.
你可是个演员   那么做太过分了
You, an actor? That's madness!
瑞秋葛瑞办公室
Rachel Green's office.
秦格
Tag.
嗨   谁打电话找我
Hi, who was that?
没有人   我只是在练习
Nobody. I was just practicing.
真的吗
Really?
嗨   嗨   瑞秋葛瑞办公室
Hi. Hi, Rachel Green's office.
你一定是西尔达
You must be Hilda. Ahem.
他是泰格   这位是菲比
He's Tag. This is Phoebe.
菲比   你能进来一下吗   嗯嗯
Phoebe, can I see you for a sec'? Mm-hm.
菲比  嗯嗯
Phoebe. Mm-hm.
这个名字很不错   你喜欢吗
That's a great name. You like that?
你应该听听我的电话号码  好吧  我们马上回来
You should hear my phone number. Okay. We'll be right back.
你为了自己雇用了那个大帅哥  对吧
So you hired yourself a little treat, did you?
我知道这样看起来像什么   菲比  但是我要告诉你
All right I know, I know how it looks, Pheebs, but I am telling you--
你不能勾搭你的助理
But-but you know you can't get involved with your assistant.
我知道  我知道雇用他  不是明智之举
Yes, I know that. I know that, and I know that hiring him was probably not the smartest thing that I've ever done.
但从现在开始   我发誓我们之间是纯公事
But, from now on, I swear this is strictly professional.
对  嘿   瑞秋
Yes. Hey, Rachel.
嗨
Hi.
你助理很帅   他什么情况
Cute assistant. What's his story?
他是  是同性恋吗  对
Is he--? Gay? Yeah.
嘿  秦瑞
Hey, Terry.
是  乔伊崔比亚尼
Joey Tribbiani.
我很惊讶像你这样的大人物   会到我们的小办公室来
I'm surprised your big head could fit through our small halls.
我得走了  乔伊   等下   泰瑞   听我说
I gotta go, Joey. Wait, Terry! Look, uh--
之前的事我抱歉
I'm really sorry about before.
我是个白痴   以为自己很大牌根本不必来试镜
I was an idiot, thinking I'm too big to audition for you.
再给我一次机会吧   我办不到
You gotta give me another chance. I can't help you Joey.
等一下  秦瑞  求求你
Wait, Terry, please!
听着  我失去了我另一份工作
Look, I just lost my other job, okay?
你不知道我多需要这出戏
You have no idea how much I need this.
求求你  帮帮我
Please, help me out.
我们是老朋友了
For old times' sake.
这家伙昏迷了五年   已经没希望了
This  poor guy's been in a coma for five years. It's hopeless.
不会的  史崔克医生最擅长展现奇迹
It's not hopeless! Dr. Stryker Ramoray is a miracle worker.
他来了
Here he comes.
早安
Good morning.
德瑞克   我是你弟弟史崔克   你听到了吗
Drake, it's your brother, Stryker. Can you hear me?
卡
And cut.
我又回来了   宝贝
I'm back, baby!
我的解释是
You know, in my defense, um...
意大利面上没有珠宝   而且我用的胶水很少
...there was no glitter on the macaroni and very little glue.
我的解释是   那个清洁妇勾引我的
And in my defense, the cleaning lady came on to me.
你现在会看时间了  对吧   会
You have no trouble telling time now right? No.
快点   现在几点了  不知道  吻男人的时间到了吗
Quick, what time is it? I don't know! Time to kiss a guy maybe?!
你在笑什么  尿布宝宝
What are you laughing at, Pampers?
你知道我说夫妻
You know when I said that because we're getting married
应该分享一切  不可以有秘密吗
that we should share everything and not have any secrets?
怎么了   那太蠢了   我们千万别那么做
Yeah? That was stupid. Let's not do that.
一点都没错
Absolutely.
我们不该把告诉彼此的秘密   再告诉其他人
And! We should keep all the stuff we told each other secret from everyone else.
一点都没错
Ha, ha. Yeah, definitely.
好吧
Okay, ha, ha.
对不起   我要跟不知道
Okay, If you'll excuse me, I'm gonna hang out with some people...
太空车事件的人去玩了
...who don't know the Space Mountain story.
我建议你别去找菲比   天啊
Then I'd steer clear of Phoebe. Man!
一点都没错   我也建议你别去找我同事
Not that you would, but I wouldn't hang out with all the guys at my office.
嗨
Hi.
你有空吗   当然  有什么事吗
Do you have a minute? Well yeah, Sure. What's up?
今天我午餐时  有两个人想约我出去
I got asked out twice today while I was at lunch...
他们都是男人
"by guys.
真的吗   对
Really? Yeah.
你有告诉别人我是同性恋吗
Did you tell someone that I was gay?
你不希望别人知道吗
Oh, did you not want people to know that?
我不是同性恋  我特别不希望  你以为我是同性恋
But I'm not gay. And I especially wouldn't want you to think I was gay.
为什么
Why is that?
我想我不该说的  你说吧
I don't think I should say. Oh, you can say.
别这样   我不希望你有事不敢告诉我
Come on, I don't want you to feel like you can't tell me things.
好吧   好吧
okay. okay.
那个  是的
Well... Yeah.
我想约你朋友菲比出去
...I'd love to ask out your friend Phoebe.
是啊  她是同性恋
Yeah, she's gay.